cedarville.edu 2019-03-31

# Privacy Policy Statement for Cedarville University Websites | Cedarville University

Cedarville University is committed to honoring the privacy of visitors to its Website. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the Cedarville University websites (*.cedarville.edu):

## Forms

All personal information filled in and sent to Cedarville University via the website's online forms, such as the Application for Admission, Event Registration, Information Request, etc., will be held confidential. This information may be shared between departments within Cedarville University and their vendors or service providers, as needed or required, but will not otherwise be sold or distributed to third parties.

## Security

Cedarville University protects the security of your personal information and honors its intended use. We carefully protect from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction the information under our control. Our websites use SSL security to encrypt transmission of personal information through the Internet. 

## Information gathering

Website tracking information is collected for statistical purposes. Analysis software creates summary statistics which can be used for such purposes as determining what information is most and least popular, assessing technical software and hardware needs, and identifying problem or performances issues.

### Cookies

In some instances, Cedarville University websites use cookies that uniquely identify your browser so that we may provide specific content that is relevant to your interests. A cookie allows the website to customize what you see based on the content that you recently viewed.

### Google Analytics Data

Google gathers data about website visitors to help site owners understand how users interact with their sites. Cedarville University uses Google Analytics Demographic and Interest Reporting and Google Ads Personalization to collect additional information about its site visitors. Cedarville University encourages its website visitors to view [Google’s Privacy & Terms](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/) page to learn how Google uses data and how you can control the data sent through your browser. Users who wish to prevent the automatic collection and use of data on the web may [Opt Out](https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en&ref_topic=2941003).

## Children under the age of 13

Children under the age of 13 should not submit any information about themselves to Cedarville University. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. In those instances that we do knowingly collect that information, we will do so only with verified parental permission before collection.

## Contacting us

If you have a concern regarding privacy issues with the Cedarville University websites, please contact us at [privacy@cedarville.edu](mailto:privacy@cedarville.edu?subject=Website%20Privacy%20Policy).
